Anahita Ahmadivarji

(704) 960-3407 anahitavarji@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Individual with experience in full-stack engineering and strong communication skills, (BA) in English. Actively pursuing a Junior Software Developer position where I can offer my passion for front-end design and expertise to work with various programming languages, including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js and React.js.

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, Javascript, Node.js, React.js
- Spanish Language- Conversational
- Farsi Language Conversational
- Excellent Written and Verbal Communication
- Highly Organized

- Enthusiastic and Coachable
- Team Player
- Results Driven
- GitHub

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ROAD TO HIRE APPRENTICESHIP *Road to Hire Coding Apprentice*

Fort Mill, SC

Sept 2020 - Present

• A rigorous six month coding program that provided in-depth knowledge and immersion of development tools and languages required to be a successful full-stack software engineer. Gained valuable development knowledge and professional skills to aid in the communication between business needs and technical requirements.

LA POBLANITA

Waitress

Charlotte, NC

Jul 2017 - Jun 2018

• Performed waitress duties in a Spanish speaking environment. Increased my Spanish language skills and successfully generated revenue in direction proportion to my customer service talent.

ZEBRA FINE DINING

Charlotte, NC

Hostess Sept 2014 - Aug 2016

• Performed hostess duties at a fine dining establishment. Focused on providing an exceptional customer experience and first impression for clientele.

EDUCATION

University of North Carolina at Charlotte

Charlotte, NC

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) English | Minor: International Studies (Dec 2019)

- **GPA:** 3.47
- **Relevant Coursework:** Study Abroad--Summer 2018 London, England | Globalization certificate, Summer 2019 Santander, Spain
- Awards & Honors: cum laude

CENTRAL PIEDMONT COMMUNITY COLLEGE

Charlotte, NC

Associate in Arts (A.A.) (Jun 2017)

CERTIFICATIONS

- Agile Project Management Certificate | Udemy (Oct 2020)
- Growth-Driven Design Certificate | Udemy (Oct 2020 Nov 2022)
- Globalization Certificate | Universidad de Cantabria (July 2019)